{"results":[{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,18000","2/3,6000"],"answer":"3","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":1741},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","2/3,15000"],"answer":"0.66","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":590},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,20000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"2","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":315},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,5000","3/2,15000"],"answer":"0.33","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":123},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","1/1,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":178},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","1/1,15000"],"answer":"0.66","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":159},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,15000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"1.5","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":83},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,15000","3/2,15000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":87},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,15000","1/1,5000"],"answer":"3","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":102},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":114},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,15000","2/3,5000"],"answer":"3","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":129},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","2/3,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":120},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,15000","2/3,10000"],"answer":"1.5","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":108},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","1/1,15000"],"answer":"0.66","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":88},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,6000","2/3,18000"],"answer":"0.33","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":113},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","1/1,20000"],"answer":"2","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":245},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":195},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,10000","2/3,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":414}]}